<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Learnura</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="introduction_at_learnura_edutech_we_prioritize_your_privacy_and_ensure_the_secure_handling_of_your_personal_information_this_policy_explains_what_data_we_collect_how_we_use_it_and_how_it_is_safeguarded_by_using_our_app_you_agree_to_the_terms_outlined_here_1_information_we_collect_1_1_firebase_authentication_we_use_google_firebase_to_manage_user_sign_ins_collecting_email_address_display_name_and_profile_picture_for_authentication_and_personalization_your_login_credentials_are_securely_stored_on_firebase_servers_1_2_learning_data_we_track_course_progress_time_spent_on_lessons_and_quiz_performance_to_customize_your_learning_experience_this_data_is_stored_locally_using_room_database_for_offline_access_2_how_we_use_your_information_personalization_tailoring_content_based_on_your_learning_behavior_authentication_secure_access_via_firebase_learning_analytics_adapting_challenges_based_on_your_progress_3_data_storage_security_firebase_handles_authentication_securely_room_database_stores_course_data_locally_for_offline_access_encryption_we_use_encryption_to_protect_your_data_4_data_sharing_we_do_not_share_your_information_with_third_parties_except_trusted_partners_like_firebase_or_as_required_by_law_5_user_rights_you_can_access_update_or_delete_your_data_at_any_time_6_contact_us_if_you_have_any_questions_please_contact_us_at_support_learnuraedutech_com"><![CDATA[Introduction At Learnura EduTech, we prioritize your privacy and ensure the secure handling of your personal information. This policy explains what data we collect, how we use it, and how it is safeguarded. By using our app, you agree to the terms outlined here. 1. Information We Collect 1.1 Firebase Authentication We use Google Firebase to manage user sign-ins, collecting: Email address, Display Name, and Profile Picture for authentication and personalization. Your login credentials are securely stored on Firebase servers. 1.2 Learning Data We track course progress, time spent on lessons, and quiz performance to customize your learning experience. This data is stored locally using Room Database for offline access. 2. How We Use Your Information Personalization: Tailoring content based on your learning behavior. Authentication: Secure access via Firebase. Learning Analytics: Adapting challenges based on your progress. 3. Data Storage & Security Firebase: Handles authentication securely. Room Database: Stores course data locally for offline access. Encryption: We use encryption to protect your data. 4. Data Sharing We do not share your information with third parties, except trusted partners like Firebase or as required by law. 5. User Rights You can access, update, or delete your data at any time. 6. Contact Us If you have any questions, please contact us at support@learnuraedutech.com]]></string>
    <string name="default_web_client_id">CLIENT_ID\n</string>
    <string-array name="category_array">
        <item>Student</item>
        <item>Teacher</item>
        <item>Both</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>